In this segment I'm going to talk about keeping your head down.
Well in baseball it's not called keeping your head down although in baseball what happens sometimes is that someone will pull their head off the ball, you've seen that and you've heard about that.
What solution, what though do they give you in baseball?
What have you heard so many times in baseball to solve moving your head?
What do they say?
Watch the bat hit the ball.
Watch the bat hit the ball, what a beautiful thought.
So that ball is coming but you're trying to watch it, you're trying to watch that bat hit the ball.
You're trying to watch that bat hit the ball.
If you're really buying into this and you want to try to hit a golf ball like a baseball, try to watch the club hit the ball, try to see it!
It's very hard to see in baseball or in golf but if you're looking down there, and you try to watch it, watch that club hit the ball, watch it!
Watch that club hit the ball, watch it!
That is the way to keep your head down.
We all know how many people move their head in golf as they come into the impact area.
Oh boy look what that does to my body but if I try to watch this club hit that ball, baseball address baseball grip, watch it hit boom!
Watch it hit, boom!
That is the greatest way to keep your head down.